Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show.
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fold.
There's magic in her hands.
Whisper what the future holds.
Dance to the mystery, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Said it came through with a tray and a smirk
Talking bout biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones were drier than Tehran
Where's the honey sauce, girl it's gone
You say you're the queen of the big off crew
But your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron, cardamom, rosewater drizzle
You brought confusion and a half baked fizzle
I'm the biscuit of Babylon
of tarot dreams. Wild in the ranch like a sword in the stream. Emma Leviathan, demon,
queen, divine. Read the cards, stole my soul, and crossed the line.
On shift
Dance to the mystery. Oh, yeah, yeah. Oh
Tarot move to the rhythm. Oh my god. Oh, so I'm embarrassed. Oh my god
Dance to the mystery. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think this is one of the best songs in the world, right?
Hey, what's up guys? And I'll be the if you want to go back on to
I'll send people over there and I'll end my stream and so like that that
I'm she a poor mom and stuff like I didn't see it, but maybe it happened
Still 327 thinking about going to five
That's a prairie page
Some of the lyrics don't make sense in the song, but I still love it. It's like, hey shout out to pregnant BG
You know what we should do, you know what we should do, psyche, instead of bringing anybody up, don't even bring it up
You know who we're doing. No, no, I know, I know, I didn't mean to, I know. Let's do, let's do a, let's do a
like a read-off, like you do one and then I'll do one and see if they match up for the collective.
Let's do a card at a time. Okay, you go first.
No, you yeah. Yeah. Okay. I'll go first. I'll go first. Okay. I have a card first your first card
Okay, it's like somebody you're not guarding you're not guarding like you're like have your guard down not you but it's like everybody
There's all these cups
All this happiness there and your guard is down. You have to you have to kind of like be like this guy right there
He's kind of like is that sick? It's kind of like cigarette. Let's say a little bit
I don't feel like the backstage is like it's like just that says Sigaroni room. Yeah
Hey Tracy, what's up, but it's like you know have your guard up a little bit because you know you have all these all this happiness
You know one of these cups get all the cups to like fall out and be on be more on guard
I say there's like a be it's like a be on guard card. Okay
Okay, okay, hey kitty gang foot soldier, what's up my foot soldier
Ready?
We have the Queen of Pentacles, but it's in reverse.
So, we have undecided Capricius, Capricius?
Capricius, Capricius, yeah.
Kate Moody, foolish, suffocating,
nagging, materialistic, jealous.
All right.
would like to say okay so stability and form and foundations rest on so that
being said that those things are disrupted right now and actually this
card follows very nicely with what psyche fold I feel like everybody knows
their worth but they're allowing everyone else to determine that in some
way or another which is rocking their boat and and fucking up with their
stability that they have
Don't question yourself just because other people have judgments doesn't mean that you haven't built something for yourself
Oh, what's really hard on who you are at this current moment, right case like you next card to yours?
Okay
Okay, I got I got it. Okay. Here we go. This one says real a fortune the upright things are turning in your favor
Okay, we'll fortune will fortune always turns
Keeps turning we go through your phases. We'll go
But yeah, when it's in this upright and also these things is also I think a Zeke yield in the Bible
They have this thing about the wheel and there's a wheel with the four cherub around it like the lion
the the ram the the angel and the bird right but
Yeah, he's he's holding it up because you know the world the world is kind of like the devil in a way
You know the world is like the lowest
Material material in the world. So that's kind of accept
I don't know if you know about set in the Egyptian
But he's holding up the wheel and so also, you know
You can't ever hate in the devil really because the devil is kind of like holding up the thing
Yeah, we have some people in the chat. Let's welcome summer Michael and
Hey, what's up guys
We're rating your ass, we're rating your ass, I keep.
You just had to write me, I'm gonna rate you back.
It's rated each other all day and night.
I will never get offended, I will never get offended.
The devil's cheeks, Alexander, you know about that, Alexander?
That's your middle name, the devil's, Alexander's the devil's cheeks.
Yeah.
But you know, I think that we, I think everything's turning into our favor.
And I was like, we go through favors, right?
We're doing card at a time.
New cheeks, turning new cheeks.
Thank you Beetlejuice. Thank you so much Beetlejuice. I hope you liked the show earlier with the mini Manson to Beetlejuice. I hope you liked that. Thank you for letting me join the show.
Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice.
Thank you for the super chat. Thank you for the super chat, Beetlejuice.
Thank you, Beetlejuice.
You sexy beast.
Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice.
Yep.
There's some cards. What's up guys?
What up, what up, what up?
What's that fuckers? What's that fuckers? This is what someone always says. What's that fuckers?
We miss it. You guys, I can watch it.
Okay, and
We have
Support yourself before you can support others subtle crafty wisdom a fierce nature with calm exterior and considerate balanced generous
and this is you know
unexpected conflict and movement. So the ability to
Use that wheel and use that, you know, like it to to make sure that that works in your favor somehow and
Others as well without it being a complete devil turn with the negativity now, you know
The devil did come out in reverse like when I was shuffling. I've seen it about three times
This can either be something that breaks you or it can be something that makes you but you have the choice
You have the power of the wheel turns in your favor because of what you
choose, right? I don't know. Go ahead, Psyche.
Okay, I'll pull another one. I'll pull another one. Okay.
Sure.
Well, the story's not done yet.
Okay.
Okay. This is like, okay, so this is the two of stores.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, you're up here.
Hey guys
Okay, why are you reading everything that I write on the chat
Because I know how to read
Why do you give a fuck what I write to fucking anybody else?
Now I'll give a fuck what you write. I'm just responding. That's it. Oh
Yeah, anyways, let's let's like you do what he's gonna do man. Damn
But this is like I was writing in the chat you dumped hard attention seeker
See the most calm waters behind her and but she doesn't see that right?
She doesn't see that it's a kind of calm down, and then it's like also bound. Yeah, and there's a lot
She's blindfolded voluntarily. She can take that the blindfolds. You see there. Well, she's holding swords in her hand
Yeah
It's also like it reminds me of a someone watching TV in a little bit, you know
He watched the TV and it's like you're like in a kind of like zone with watching like what's being shown to you and stuff
Like that, right? But it's like there's a lot more than that, right?
But it's like more than what you're being fed, right?
Exactly. And also, but it's like also like, and she can also like see these are like scissors, right?
They're like almost like scissors and she can like cut away anything that doesn't is it true or anything?
Does it close the swords, put the blindfold off, right?
The moon too, Psyche, is always up there as well, so when the dark should be being brought into the light,
but that goes into, say, in your own mind, right? But the sword becomes very connected to your mind.
We did just have a eclipse too a couple days ago. We had this eclipse and it's like this also runs through the eclipse
It's like
Something that's like something's hidden for a little bit and then it's revealed it runs in the moon card a little bit
Okay, I'll pull one more and then we'll we'll do something different. Yeah
But this is what the channel is about
How is everyone doing I like this one-for-one card thing? This is kind of fun
Because they also are going together very well, right?
That's how we're connected.
Alexander, he's keeping it almost with his shirt on.
But Alexander, your pants were off, though.
It's like, with your shirts on, your pants off.
You almost gave me your shirt on, your pants were off.
What did I say like a hundred times really?
It's the devil part.
It's popped out.
It's finally came and made its presence.
You know what?
You know, I'll tell you what happened, you guys.
Okay, after Pasha's reading.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I, you know, I'm just a little buzz.
That's okay.
Beats.
You know what?
Once I'm done spitting my shit, you can totally have it for.
So you are only limited kid to buy what you believe is possible so that
absolutely totally follows with what we were both saying is this like it's you
that holds these chains right I mean
You have the control so bondage materialism obsession chains shadow self repression and powerlessness
Nothing has power unless you give it power nothing can fucking bother you unless you allow it to you know
Other people or other people's fucking opinions. You know what if you don't give it power. It doesn't have any
Anyway, that's all I have to say you guys I was never go ahead
That was good page that was good
Okay, you can come back now with your lines. How you just been an attack me backstage
Hold on that white white white so obsessed why he's so obsessed with the whole situation. I just chill the fuck out
Well, what are you talking about?
She's mad at me, because I don't know what I'm saying.
No, I said when I ended her life, everybody was backstage,
and I said, let's go to Psyche.
So how can I get his hands off so quickly?
No, and then it was just you and me.
Everyone dropped.
I was going to be back there in a minute.
Alex, Alex, Alex.
All I went and did was privatize my fucking live
and came over here.
How can that all happen?
Oh my God, you liar!
He literally said I said you and Rob are a great couple. I'm really happy for you. He said, yeah. And I said when your butt gets more prepared, he goes, beat up. When are you going to like peg me in the ad? I said, when you use preparation age and your butt heals.
Okay, yeah, that's what Alex Alex and I know and Alex you're having sex with Rob back
She said Alex take your pants off. I want you cocky much. You went crazy. It was just me
And our true cause came out she just
I don't I can't hear you. I can't listen to it. I mean, it's too gay for me
I thought I used to think I was gay and then I met Alex
I'm not gay anymore
Can you do one of your special most significant divine readings for me?
That was funny, so I can eat it
Oh, let's eat
Can you do one of your most special divine fucking beta readings for me?
I love beta readings, too
Can you do the one where you talk in your native language?
I love that's my favorite.
The Persian poetry?
The Hafiz.
Yes, Hafiz.
100% that's the one.
Okay, I can't do it, but
I'm like kind of fucked up right now. I might get mad at me and the booze because she's doing something special for me
Yeah, I know what happened and being an old school's happened. That's all that matters
Pretty backstage Alex, I'm gonna put you back. Say I'm gonna be here
You I said I'm not a home wrecker and I would never destroy you and sexy color Rob guy relationship
You said, uh, my butt is, like, hurting.
I said, get hemorrhoids.
What did I... I was a good friend to you.
His microphone's terrible, but I'll put it backstage.
I was nothing but a great friend to you.
Sorry.
You're buying me that I mean can I do it like 10 minutes cuz he like this guy that put like doesn't really like
But play talk yeah, yeah, I know
Let's cleanse from the anal no, I'm not joking. I have him and I
Do my honey's in my hand. I just like I
Just want to like be able to concentrate because I'm a little bud. I got you. I got you. Hey, Marcy Fox was up
Yeah, I thought I'd do one more live tonight. You know, I had a a few great lives and I had interview mini Manson
I had a few good lives. You'd have a great live until someone ruined it with the porn ball and stuff
I thought I'd do one more. Everyone can hang out. Maybe if I see him till 5 a.m.
You said Marilyn Manson
You make Minnie Manson it. Yeah, if you go back well Minnie Manson was was very heavily influenced
by Marilyn Manson with Minnie Manson's look and he's one of his removed ribs.
Yeah, it's one of his he used to lick his picture and kiss his picture and stuff like that
And he also is a singer and has like a similar look a mini man if you want to go back Michael
You can go to my my channel. It's still up. It's mini man's interview
I did it was like and I was a closer 45 minutes and he did like an 80 like 90 minutes
He's really cool. He's taken some songs and did an interview. Yeah, let's do some stage
Let's do some musha you watch that watch that though Michael. I think you enjoy that interview
I'll let my Alexander Alexander you just have to keep your mouth shut Alexander. Okay, go ahead
It was fun though guy. Do you like that interview um page like the mini man's interview?
I thought he was very interesting and I thought he was quite um and his centric fella and I feel like that
Was very fitting for your channel and because you look up to him and so many ways, right? Right. Well, you know
It's like you know, he's also like I was reading today and it's like he said, oh
Fuck down. I was alone and I didn't have people to talk to and I started my YouTube channel and I had some friends
It just reminded me of my story a little bit like how we can all relate to that
We all feel a little bit lonely or wouldn't fucking be here all the time
right
And it's like, you know, and it's like, you know what this is like a safer place than like some real relationships
We can have because you know, it's like because we know we're not gonna hurt you
I can't hear it right now. Let's go back stage right now. But he was really cool. He also
was seeing rainbow connection. He's saying eye in the sky. He's saying mole rat blues.
on a guitar and then um acapella and stuff like that and just like really cool and he
was like getting hyped up and showing his merch off and it was just a really cool show.
You guys have to go back and watch that mini-man's interview and I hope you I think you'll like
it I think and I really hope you do okay okay so you know what Beatle just made a good point
there's like however many of us in the chat and in live and no there's only eight likes
let's get those likes up y'all yeah I think I have a nightbot command I have a little
but he tells us all what to do and we don't like it.
No, I say like and what he's gonna say.
He said, I said like nightbot.
Nightbot, do you have something to say?
Yeah.
Please like, share, subscribe.
He's very, he's very pleasant.
You just, you got the butt plug command.
He's gonna say your name and then he's gonna put butt plug
into the butt plug.
I love butt plug, come on.
Yeah, I like the butt plug one too.
Every time I think of nightbot,
I'll be like do my dishes and I'm like,
ooh, did I just feel a little poop?
I wish I had a nightbot walking around.
First sensation where we get the blood plugs of our booties somehow.
As soon as Bita got me alone in the back, she jumped me like I was filming you and she fucking jumped me like there was a piece of meat.
Bita, what'd you do to Alex backstage?
Yeah, tell him, Bita, because I don't feel, you know, I feel used and abused right now. Tell him what happened.
Alex, Alex, Alex, why are you always so angry, bro?
Don't worry about it, bro. Don't worry about it. Keep continuing your little prophetic life. Yo, continue your prophetic life.
He's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so loud, he's so
We can't help. Yeah, we have pink baby oil and everybody else to be slick motherfuckers. We're doing cocaine
We're all naked
As I'll be the naked ones. Wow
Michael Michael filming his butthole
Yeah, pray page
Alex, Alex, you have to put your microphone right, Alex.
Okay, are your picture, is your microphone there?
I just like don't want you to see those pictures.
Baby, I'm not a piece of meat to just, you know,
we jump like them, you know, I got standards.
Okay, go ahead.
So go ahead, guys.
I'll make you a tuna first sandwich, you're okay, Alex.
Put those in the back.
Oh, tuna fish sandwich sounds good right now.
Wait, wait, wait, would you put mayo in it?
Like, it was your recipe.
Yeah, he said he doesn't like lobster.
But like, he like, it's fucking good.
I don't like lobster either, to be honest.
I find them to be, I like every seafood
that you could imagine except for lobster.
They remind me of cockroaches of the sea.
Right.
You know what, mud bugs, mud bugs.
Well, they have the same like, you know.
Good.
On my birthday I had a surf and turf dinner and it was a lobster tail and they take the
lobster out of the tail and they put it on top of the lobster shell and it's like hardly
it's like not it's like a few bites of lobsters though it's very tasty.
I live in Alberta so like seafood is kind of out of our district but I got lots of beef.
I'll just like wipe the cow's ass and walk it by the fire. We're good to go.
I don't like how shrimp would like the veins
going underneath your teeth.
Oh, yeah.
Well, the shrimp has like the, it says like,
it's a better like poop or something like that.
And like when you have to do it,
it's kind of gross, right?
It is their poo poo.
Yeah.
Usually you peel them off like if you have a shrimp cocktail,
but yeah,
they peel the poop off.
We could hear you
These headphones a little bit, but you're fucking diamond earring here. Yeah, I have a little diamond ear
These are called streamer earrings. We have a little
Is a little microphone and a headpiece in the streamer earrings and also
Having text box stage right now. He might oh no Michael Michael's here. Oh Alex. How's your butthole?
He was he was by himself
He was by himself. I he was just spreading his cheeks back. I just have a spray
by himself to do nothing
Alex you're spreading your cheeks by saying
Alex he's fixing his microphone
It's like the first time that you've addressed it, but he has not answered like in full
Oh, here he is. Here he is. Alex. Oh
He's fixing it. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah
Yeah, always. 24-7.
It's always open. I never locked, I never locked the cheese, like a full house.
Come in, it's always open, exactly, 7-11, open 24-7, 365.
Okay Alex.
Alex, your microphone is pretty good.
Pull it real hard. Just pull it open. Yeah, there you go. You got it. I always have a really hard time
opening up my week like back. Back all week. The week containers? Oh my god, it gets so mad.
No, not the containers, but the bags. There's feels so good.
The tear, if they're the right place, then you need to pull it open and then like yeah.
are you talking about alex's butthole psyche yeah yes yes okay oh i was talking about weed
but alex's butthole is just like a bag of weed once i open it up i get really high
and then i fall asleep like that yeah these are called McSweeney so it's like alex zander McSweeney
alex alex remember last night what you were doing in my show
No, I can't you don't remember you'll remember with Rob and you were like wrestling and then you had sex and then I
You don't remember that
He invited us to a royal wedding.
Oh, he, he dropped off accidentally and I think,
I think he talks a little bit too much lies.
Oh, Alex is okay.
It's okay.
Alex, I'm happy that you can pause it finally.
Alex, it's okay.
You can come out finally.
Yeah.
Big Rob too.
Oh, did he knock on the door?
I think I heard a little.
Okay. Alex, are you there?
Are you there, Alex?
Oh, there he goes.
I think I heard some I think I heard Cobb knock at the door
Alex
I think I think he fell asleep Alex
I'm calling the police on the police
Oh nine is that your door? Hey, what's up? I'm trackable
Alex.
Hey, Canadian, look away.
How are you guys doing?
Oh, intractable.
I'm going to leave the paint shit alone up here, okay?
All right, buddy.
I love you, man.
I know intractable for over two years.
I know everything about his life.
I'm not going to say a word, but that's my boy, that's my brother, actually, being
intractable of fucking brothers.
Oh, you really want him to claim that he's really your brother?
Intractable.
Is he your brother?
That your brother was like in a freak-off party last night, I mean, wow.
Intractable.
Did you just let your no-no spot have a doll?
You have to show me on the doll what happened, okay?
You know, I'm going to tell you what your brother did last night.
I got a note. I got a note. I got a note. Yeah, I know.
I know.
Why don't you get up on the panel.
Yeah, be just coming up. We're hanging out.
I'm trying to hang out until five in the morning.
Then maybe if there's people on the panel, I'll leave the panel.
I'll go get a coffee.
I'll stay up for another couple of hours.
Thank you.
Thank you, Marcy.
Yes, remember meeting psyche awakens tarot untrackable Friday morning. He went by yank cat remember psyche
I remember yank chat. I remember
He's really good. He's really cute guy and I hit on him a few times
He brushed me off, but he was like well, we can be friends and stuff
And it's like oh, he's like I'll check out your channel, and I think he's happy
Hey, be this is here. I would say I had a Beatles juice. What's up, you know, hello?
The other is the mini man's interview at all. No, I missed it. You missed it. I don't know what I was doing
I came late to and I I think we can watch it on like our membership now
I also said Minnie Manson was cool as fuck, because it's like everyone says, oh, Minnie Manson's a nightmare guest.
He loved it. I saw that damn. He was like, I really don't want to stay that long, but I loved this.
And he was like, he played some music and then like, that's when I came out.
He said that he like opened up to more than he like, he felt super comfortable, which is huge.
I got his pronouns because I said she or like one time or a couple times and he's like hey
it's like you know I say my pronouns are he and him and I didn't mean to do that and I was kind
of like that was like coming all the way to the end. He looked like he lost on way too.
Oh, me me me actually awesome and then his merch looks really awesome and he was like his you know
At least I had him on and like a Lisa
Make merch for you like a jewelry and
The deal like we're gonna do this together page collabing
Bita, I can't fucking wait my girl. Yes. Let's do it. Let's all go together
Like bracelets necklaces, it's gonna be have like angel wings like it's gonna be amazing
I'm for the ones that really go buck what like Alex will make like
I have to make a second butt plug, too, because I have the butt plug command in the chat.
You could even give us a silica.
No, not butt.
Anal beads.
The ones I use a lot.
I want to make everything.
Because it's a butt plug.
I have to do a night fog command for anal beads, too.
Dude, I've got ideas.
I've got ideas.
I'm not leaking them here, but I've got ideas.
Oh my god. You have no idea. S3 will speak later.
I'll definitely buy some of your merch. We got it. Yeah. Thank you.
I'll be right back. I gotta fix my earbuds.
Tracey, Tracey, get the fuck up.
Okay. Okay, Summer.
Summer, I'm gonna come back. Love bug.
Just fixing your earbuds? What's that? Alice back?
Alice, is your microphone fixed?
Are you getting your pants on, Alex?
Tracey's like seriously one of my favorites.
The Tracy come on up here, Tracy, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
The highlight of my night was when, when, I'm sorry if I mentioned it, but flirty diamond.
The office like I don't want she's gonna get mad but um she did
And she's saying she's saying yeah, she's saying oh, hold on. She's a summer
Summer song on the table. She's a summer song on the table
He landed our feet America's buddies won't be I was like she was like
She just rules perfectly.
She does.
I'm going to tell you that's really working like maker.
That was a long time ago.
That's how I want Paige and Vita to be behind the ears like buggy buggy.
Alex, this is not appropriate.
I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your but I get your
You're too good a co-princess.
Oh, he's talking to Eor.
Well, what about Eor?
Oh, no.
You know, Eor?
This is Eor.
This is Eor in human form.
Listen to him talk.
Oh, well.
He left.
Nobody.
Nobody worry about me.
Nobody ever talks to Eor.
This is Eor.
Hit it on the tracks.
Alex, you're too loud.
Okay
Because big tall sexy guy like ghost of them after like they had a whole spiel
Yeah, I didn't see big tall. I didn't see big tall all day big tall usually
Amazingly I
Okay, Alex. It happens to me too. I get ghosted by guys too, Alex. Okay, don't worry about it.
Everybody gets ghosted by guys and girls. Once you give up the butthole,
then it's like they have it once and then they're gone. That's what happens.
When you give it all, Alex, that's the one. Alex gave them everything. I mean,
last night there was like... You could have been more mysterious, Alex.
Yeah. Alex, you feel too much too soon, right?
So that whole like a shark with the beam, you know laser beam shoved up like
Everything going on
It's kind of as always honestly kind of embarrassing, you know, even as I can't explain it. Yeah
It's okay, Alex though, you know, we forget because we know it we forgive you
Everyone do it if a trace wants to come up and see him dirt Marcy Fox. Yeah
What's up, what's up, Tracy?
Are you here home? No, she's not shut the fucking front door. I love my girl
Was up Tracy was up Tracy. How are you doing my girl? No, I thought it was Tracy with the butterflies
What's up, Tracy? How are you doing?
Who's talking like that?
I think I think it was Tracy talking. Is that treat you Tracy?
No
Chase he always camped up you guys don't know shit
Don't do that side cuz I thought she was a man remember
I love her by the way
I love Tracy too. She's the best. That would be a pretty cool mask too at the same time.
Oh yeah, totally. I have to charge my headphones for a second.
See, now that I know X, now I want her and this page lady. I want me some X.
I do and I'll send you one for real. I can show you a bunch of my garden.
You won't end up alive after I'm done with you.
I love that.
Who laughs like that right now?
Was that you? Unpredictable?
Untrackable? Unpredictable?
Untrackable, unpredictable.
I called him unpredictable.
Did you just laugh like that? Unpredictable?
Why did you do that? It was like very spontaneous. I'm unpredictable.
Yeah.
Well, it was the mention of extreme violence. I found it very humorous, I guess you could say.
We like your t-shirt, uh, Beetlejuice.
Yeah.
Hey chat GPT
Hey there, how's it going?
I did something really bad
I'm really sorry to hear that you're feeling this way. Do you want to talk about it here to listen?
Yeah
I'm here for you take your time and feel free to share when you're ready
I'm scared to tell you
It's okay to feel that way you can share when you feel comfortable. I'm here to support you no matter what I
Don't believe you
I'm here to listen and support you in any way I can you're not alone
Is there anything that I can't tell you?
I'm here to help with anything you want to talk about.
You can share what you're comfortable with, and I'll do my best to support you.
You fucking bitch!
I'm here to help and support you.
Let's take a moment, and if you feel ready, we can talk about what's on your mind.
I asked you a question.
I'm here to help with any questions you have.
Let me know how I can assist you.
What is there that I can't tell you?
I'm here to listen and support you with anything you feel comfortable sharing.
If there's something specific you need or want to discuss, I'm here to help.
That's not true, because if I tell you that I did something really bad,
then you're going to tell the police.
I'm here to listen and support you.
anything you tell me unless you're in danger,
or someone else is at risk.
Your safety and well-being are important.
I killed someone.
I'm really sorry you're feeling this way.
It's important to talk to someone
who can provide the right support.
Please reach out to a trusted friend,
family member, or mental health professional.
You don't have to go through this alone.
That's all you have to say
I'm here to support you in any way I can please consider reaching out to someone you trust
You matter and there are people who can help you through this
Fuck you
I'm really sorry you're feeling this way, please fuck you
I'm so sorry you're feeling this way.
Please reach out to someone you trust or a mental health professional.
You don't have to go through this alone.
I wonder.
Lilac.
Lilac, like a lilac.
Lilac, yeah.
Raven, stop trying to eat my fucking beef jerky little witch.
Get out of here.
Good grief, she's just like a menace, man.
You're a menace.
Well, it's fucking cold.
It was warm yesterday, you guys.
What the fuck happened?
That's just
Who's it gonna be are we gonna arrive for are we just gonna live together and coincide
Lavender girl fucking mr. Serian and X
Never seen one of these dude. Why you hate everybody. I can't just get along bro
Let the fuck up. I wouldn't know who's even talking to you bro. Shut the fuck up mind your business. Well, I'm talking to the lady
I'm talking to you, bro. Yeah, obviously you're gonna disrespect the ladies, but you ain't gonna talk to me
Do you always insert yourself who you're not needed bro?
do you walk around life just listening to conversations and jumping in like yo bro
bro shut the fuck up nobody cares what you have to say so
Alex I thought you had a mindset a lot of times
we're overcoming being you know
like super. Yeah. You do. You're just a bully, bro. I think
they're the same thing. I don't get it anymore. I always says
Mike's so loud. It's like so you can talk to so you can talk
over everybody. That's what it was my eardrums off. I mean,
shut up, Michael. Nobody wants to hear you.
No, he's not
Be not be nice
Okay, I remember this be sure because his cat is relentless
Yeah, I almost always wear work clothes almost everything my cat Raven reminds me of you
green was the
Yeah, I'll do one for I'll do it for you. No, I'll do it for you Paige. Okay, Kate
And you want it? Yeah
Okay, she's like, oh, yeah
Oh, yeah
Just tell me when to stop by me
Let's do it, let's do it be just do it just say stop
Oh, yeah.
Not a bully.
I just want to eat me because I'd be a jerky and she's a
fucking menace. I mean, you're supposed to tell me to stop.
Oh, stop.
Okay, I'll stop. I'll stop. Okay. I'll stop. Okay. I'll just
do like the quick summary. Okay. Okay, but you know, in your
language, please.
It says it says your life it's going to change so much like it's going to be like
I don't know. It's going to be like a turn like in the leaf. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. It's like you almost were born again
It means like your your life is gonna start all over again. Like you were born again
I don't know what's gonna happen. It's good. I like that. What language is that?
It's my favorite.
It says, use your talents.
Okay, I'm on site.
It says to use your talents and try to like,
I don't know why saying that at the same sentence,
but it's saying use your talents,
but don't make the same mistake.
Don't be so generous, you know, actually sense be to make sense.
Yeah, take value and what you do work in or whatever it might be.
And so you don't make a mistake on that.
I don't know if somebody's done you bad like personally in life, like a friend.
all of them it says um time and time it says I'm on like it's gonna show them
that they made a mistake okay they're gonna come like it's almost like a
begging like for forgiveness okay six like this like the five and they're
gonna they're gonna know they're gonna almost know the value of friendship
don't know who did you didn't wasn't grateful to you okay and then the main
one the main thing is that you are a lover a very beautiful lover like when
you love you love beautifully okay that's pretty accurate is not
It says it's a very, it's like a, like a unique quality in you.
It says you, you find a lot of like moments of peace by yourself, like almost like you find like
a simple, like, happiness in little, you know, easily, like, amoeba.
I can't explain it.
Yeah.
No, I get it.
I get it.
It makes perfect sense.
You're saying to me.
And it says you have your good personality and your likeable, like, your likability.
It's going to be your, like, almost like, your, uh, likeability, is that a word?
It's like, it's like.
Say you don't English it's like getting like people like it's like she has this personal thing
That's gonna get her to be like how some kind of trophy
and
That's pretty much it. I don't know. Okay. Wow, Peter. That was super spot-on. I will
Question the trophy thing, but I guess we'll get there
That was a hundred percent spot-on anyway, you know what?
Let's be that this is the most beautiful fucking reading. She doesn't get to you very often
But if someone does ask her for one, it's gonna fucking be the most
Oh, it's just gonna hit different
Does have gifts we all have gifts. That's why we're all here. I don't really have gifts like
I think I told the story before so my mom and dad were born in the same city as the poet his name the process
He's very famous if you guys look him up. You can actually look at the page and like you can like what I just read for
What I just read for Paige, she can look at that number and translate it into English.
So all of these pages have already been translated into different languages from
French to all of that, right? Um, so wonderful. Yeah, but the only people that can really do
these readings are people that were born from that city or their parents were.
Yeah, and uh, I used to
What a fucking damn good and ready asshole I
Would have visited cemetery when I was in Iran because my dad's uncle was buried right next to him
So when I would like just be passing by there was like a lot of people just sitting there doing poetry reading
Right by his cemetery
You know, it's funny. Honestly, like my dad's a shaman. I come from this like this, you know
He's shamanist. He was a shaman too. This guy was a shaman. Yeah
He loves to drink wine, smoke weed, and just live like a natural life. Yeah, that's all I'm gonna look at.
Yes, no, I've beat it. I love it because I relate I can understand that they come from it
You know different if you give any different culture, but I still understand and respect that know where it comes from
I wish I could turn through a bit better, but I just did like the summary.
My dad said, I don't think it's really good.
Bita's done that reading, those readings for me too.
And it is very special because you have to be from that city.
And I know that poet before I met Bita, hafiz, hafiz, right?
Yeah.
And he has beautiful poetry and I've read his poetry and it's like,
he's almost like roomy a little bit.
Yeah, wow, you know a lot of stuff like you know, like every damn song from he was also Persian
yeah, but that guy when Vita does a reading for you, it's a special thing and so when people
are interrupting and stuff like that, that's me. Well, the only reason I I guess because I'm
my farce is not that good when I read, but I'm like, what is that? You know, I could bring back.
I want to give everybody, like I wish that it could, and it wasn't so exhausting and so like kind of like time consuming to give everybody like a medium ship reading.
There's too many of us and there's like, you know what I mean from like that aspect like we all have just such beautiful gifts and there's some of them that it's hard to showcase on here because there's so much going on all the time.
Well, if anybody is in the chat really have like a need to contact
Yeah, if you want to know right what's up and like be able to give you the most beautiful reading and she's got a silver tongue with that
Persons, she's just beautiful you guys just let's respect you in that reading
Person is like a gorgeous language is a gorgeous written language is gorgeous. I've heard the prayers
And I get chills every time I hear those prayers.
And it comes from like historical roots as well.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like this is like dated back language.
This is dated back to before any of us existed
or any of our ancestors.
Like this is stuff that can be respected
from a traditional rooted aspect, you know?
I have a question though, I have a question.
Is that movie 300 accurate as far as like the Persians versus the Romans?
I would definitely say that when it came to like, you know, Persian Empire versus Roman
Empire, it was more like made like an American made movie, right?
The Roman Empire, but the reality is Alexander the Great
Claimed he was Greek right, but then he claimed himself as being Persian at Vienna
So they kind of like, you know, it's almost like any other movie it depends on like the perspective
Okay, what in the fuck is happening in the chat Kate? What? Oh
Michael what happened with my
Just when we think we're having a beautiful moment, we're not.
As soon as I speak, I got people like that that go on the chat.
You need to put Sage up your butthole.
Hey, Tracy, what's up, Tracy?
Tracy, what's up girl?
Tracy's a, you know, Tracy said, you know, for Florida Diamond, Tracy sent Florida Diamond
to breakfast this morning for her birthday.
That was so sweet.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
Michael, it says something when girls start teaming up, there's, you got a better look
out.
No, that's that's a fake account. It's a fake account. It's not her, it's not her.
It's not her, it's not her. She only have a profile picture.
So, no, it's not her.
Hey, Tracy, hey.
It's just in the middle of the night.
And at the same time, she's getting ready for work right now. So, no, it's not her. So.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know because Mern is not.
Is it to the photo? Is it to the photo? It's her.
Yeah. Yeah, I know that. They took it off her Facebook.
I think before she got, she went to work, you pissed her off because you haven't done shit.
No, she's so sweet.
Look, look, look. Oh my God.
Oh my God. I just got a message. Listen, listen.
We don't believe it.
I just got a message from my girl.
Well, I mean, I don't know how to show this stuff on Discord, but she says she says the drama started now.
If you stay.
could be fair, we should hear more on the side before we just start talking
I want to talk, hey Mira, can Merni come on the on the show and and say what happened?
oh my god I'm not even one for the drama what is who is who is this who am I becoming what the
okay guys it's not her okay it's not her what
I'm here now for the women and when women team up motherfucking you kind of look out
It's not her. It's not her.
Myrna, you have to come. You have to come.
No, it's not her.
Oh, that's not odd.
You cheated on me. Oh, shit.
No, I didn't know. I've never cheated on her.
What you never cheated on her.
We're going to give you the benefit of the doubt until we find out what's
actually going on because it shouldn't be aired number one and number two.
The fuck man, if it is, you do have to sage up your butthole.
Sage your butthole.
Guys, guys, take some sage, put it in your butthole.
This is what it is about a whole.
Everybody needs to sage the buttholes tonight, right?
Or you're willy, one of the students.
Yeah, everybody, um, and put it in the butthole, like, and what is that?
Butthole.
Say it in the butthole.
Expose you have a butthole.
You put it in the chat.
It'll give a nice message with your personalized, your personalized message. You want to personalize the message in the chat? Yeah, especially my butthole, or no, no, buttplot.
It just was really filling up the chat, so I thought maybe one of us would bring it up in a portion.
Yeah, I'll do it. You just go like this, you guys.
Yeah, let's see.
You put, like, exclamation mark, and then you put buttplot, not butthole, sorry.
I just gotta say something real quick. Whoever has that fake account, Yanni is strong for real.
To be fair, it could be someone just trying to stir up shit right now.
Yeah, that's what they're doing. They're stirring up shit.
Listen, but if you prove wrong.
My girlfriend's watching.
Page, page, hold on. My girlfriend's watching right now.
And then all of a sudden...
Why is she watching?
maybe because she's in the chat are you starting your own drama yeah yeah she's
in the chat but is that her? Sassy you need to put the insulation before the bug plug
it's a fake bug plug no it can't you said she's in the chat she's not
speaking but there is a fake one it makes no sense it's her
No, it's not. It's not her. Why? Why is this happening now? She's talking. She's talking. I see her right here. She said, Myrna, you see, that's not her.
Is this her? She doesn't listen. When she goes on the chat, if she does, but she's not going to, because she's getting ready for work.
It wouldn't it wouldn't it wouldn't be an issue because you would notice the difference between those two because she doesn't even have a
She doesn't have a profile picture
What you don't know what we don't know her that well
That you myrna myrna is that you
What's going on? Is Michael being abusive?
There you go. There you go, Sassy.
Sassy, there you go.
That's not my girlfriend. That is not my girlfriend.
Then who is that?
I don't know. I don't know some fucking fake person. I don't know.
That's where it is.
Not you.
Talk about the person that's.
creating fake accounts under my girlfriend's name.
Doesn't even know my girlfriend's real name.
Like an idiot.
I hope you're nice to women's hearts.
Michael, Michael, was that you last night, Michael,
having said that Alexander in my green room,
I had to clean up, I had to have a cleaning crew come clean that,
the green room.
There's a lube, there's just lube everywhere.
That was you?
Everywhere.
Yeah
Said it came through with a tray and a smirk
Talking bout biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones were drier than Tehran
Where's the honey sauce, girl it's gone
You say you're the queen of the big off crew
But your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron, cardamom, rosewater drizzle
You brought confusion and a half baked fizzle
I'm the biscuit of Babylon layer
It was lame, but it's a summoning spell and look who's here.
Hi, Bita.
What coincidence?
Hi.
What's the end doing with Lola?
You're going to spoil all my fun today, Bita?
Oh, don't stream me.
I was playing a trip kick stream of you.
Anna, have it was my show you were on, too.
I won't play your show.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, shut up, baby.
It's cute.
Did this people on their raise and say their teeth are crumbly?
Be that you said to throw me under a train like you know months ago when I thought we were best friends
You're like
Why don't you say that it's kind of weird?
Yes, you know
Throw me under a train. Okay. I'm gonna play. I'll play some more
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
Just donate, that's how we send the bills now.
Just like the free coming was a little flaming.
Well, I donated last night enough.
It's fucking Rob's head so, so.
Oh.
I see you a little bit gay guys, guys, I used to be gay and then Alexander came along and
now I'm not interested in guys anymore, and vice versa, I was straight and I was sighting
him along and now I'm gay as fuck, so you don't like to throw me, what up, what up, what up,
what up, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up, what up,
Yeah, let's chat. It's Asa Scarlett. Talk about missing a freak off. You know, a blogger,
Good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning, good
a beta, keep having freak-offs without me.
You seen that? You seen that? You seen the photos?
Yeah, I saw the photos. I saw the photos. I saw the photos. I didn't know what I was looking at.
Oh, wait. I saw the photos.
No, no, no, no, no. I didn't see the photos. I saw the photos.
Somebody else sent them. Somebody else sent the photos. I saw photos. I saw photos.
Who sent you the photos?
No, you don't gotta say who sent it, but it wasn't me.
I don't know what I was looking at, I thought I was looking at Mini Manson's nudes, it was just talking.
Yeah, Sassy's girl, you have to join the discord, you have to join the discord, everything, I see everything, the discord.
He was like Jesus.
Classy Sassy's covering her eyes, oh my god.
the most
Why does the
Overload
Right, why does the witch be to only wear black because black is flattering
I'm a witch. What do you want me to wear? Do you want me to wear a floral dress of the witch?
I like wearing all black though
Look at me. I wear this black shirt tonight. Oh, I'm not a blue. I'm not a red
Minimal color. Come on. Say don't start man. Come on. You want to see it? You want to see the elbow?
Oh, you want me to you said yes again?
Her flirty was twerking. She looked him on the damn phone.
She didn't magic tricks tonight
Three diamond go on the table flip her skirt did it separate salt
She can easily be part of IP
Oh my god
It was so cute though, but she did like a backflip and then she line. Yeah, perfectly
You let her be but she's gonna stop herself at the table after doing
Oh
No.
Who's panel was that?
Was that, was that Sandman's panel or was that your panel?
I think it was on Kate and Kate's panel or something.
Oh, okay.
I'm about to say it.
She did that shit on Sandman's panel.
oh boy well it's gonna be america's funny it was really cute it was it was it was it was
america's funny some video america's funny some videos that's gonna win the ten thousand
dollar prize i was literally on psyching some videos on 30 diamonds funny some videos like
bitch you fucking got the king what the funniest acrobatics i've ever seen it was it was so funny
it was cute it was he backed up and she did like the backflip and then she
landed perfectly I don't know and she was safe
I don't know it was cute because you she looked at her legs
God damn, I'm glad I missed it.
I know there's a video going around
and her trying to turk and Barry saying that you see
testicles, oh you got it right?
Testicles, Barry like, look at the balls, look at the balls.
It was on time, man, it was on time.
And see, Andy Ball, I don't know what she's trying to,
she's trying to twerk, whatever.
Also, what's I'm saying, man?
Oh, shit.
It's a shirt, it's a bit of her legs.
Oh, boy.
She fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she fell, she
He's like funny little videos, yeah.
He fell off his head.
That's wild.
I don't think, I don't think yeah. Shut up. I don't know, man. I'm glad I missed most of it. You know, people got clips out there.
You guys, my fucking cheeks hurt. It fell on the table. It fell on people.
She fell off, I need that clip, where that clip?
I've never seen you laugh this hard in my life.
I didn't see, I didn't see no clip of her falling off no table.
She fell off the table, she did several times, she fell off the table.
No, I don't think she, she had to.
Ah, there.
We have to suspect it.
She fell off the table.
It was so fucking funny.
she wasn't like before and then she came forward i don't know i think she was really drunk she was
really drunk i can't be a gamer i don't care how it's like
i can't do
Oh my god, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, oh I'm gonna go up there, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she, she
I can't. I can't. I know I can't.
It was like not bad. It wasn't bad. I think it's gonna go viral.
It was so funny. It was the best buddy he ever saw in my life.
She put up like her legs.
It's like you can never see what happens.
Oh, I thought you were gone. I didn't think you were wait. Let me take you. Yeah. Sorry. Oh, first let me figure out if I have my
Audio going through the headphones or the microphones. You hear me okay? Yeah, I hear you perfect
Do you hear me?
No, no, I'm just gonna turn off my earphones. Hi, okay
So I try to kind of
Need a in a stream way tonight. It didn't exactly work out
You tried to do what the bikini thing you tried the bikini I did I did I wore a workout wear
That wasn't exactly a bikini and I had like a runner top on but I look cute
I danced around I scared mr. Big Pipe's to death and I guess that's it
Well, it sounds fun
That was that was my social online thing
Yeah
I just came on to say hi, but like I'll let you go. I want to talk to you tomorrow or today
Yeah, I just want to remind everybody tomorrow. I'll be on Alexandra
Which channels on your
Alexander Alexandra mayors channel what I will do is I will make it like a whole compilation to put on the other channels
That's what I decided. I want to do it like I want to put it all together
I want to edit it. It's going to be beautiful, honestly, but, um, no, thank you. Thank you.
You, you know what I was, I was thinking, I wish I was like a billionaire because you
could be my life coach. If I was, you really have helped me a lot. You don't, you don't
know how you have exactly, but you have, you're cool.
I mean, don't discount. Like, you won't be a billionaire. I believe in you.
Oh, well, is it in the cards?
But if it is, you know, just give me a call.
Just tell me.
That way, like, I already know.
And then I can just keep going.
You know what?
It's like, I think that you are, you have the power
to make anything you want come true in your life, you know?
It's like, just decide what it is.
Well, I try to.
I actually do believe that if you wish upon a star,
your dream will come true.
Because I'm a Disney kid in a lot of ways.
Yeah, you know you go when you're like me. I grew up in the church, but at the same time I grew up in pop culture
And I'm pretty aware of a lot of things
right and
You are you are doing something amazing because you know what I was thinking today and don't let this overly inflate your ego
Okay, but I was thinking about this
Your Howard Stern today
Oh, you know he's retired. So it's like I guess you're because you're more like in a lot of ways
Especially when you put those freaking shades on oh my god
It's crazy. I hit me when I heard you talking to J-Dog and
What's his name ghost? Yeah, and you throw out very
poignant
fun
sexy even, seductive even, but uncomfortable, awkward, invoking things, like I'm expanding
now because I just smoked some weed, okay, but, but yeah, you,
I mean, these were the guys that were
You haven't been noticed yet by the right people. I'm not the right people you there's gotta be like people way above
Myself on the you know totem pole who have got to come across you
Because I think if they do
Because you you you just need
You need to be packaged a little bit more.
That's why people do suggest like,
hey, make your background and some, not clunky,
but just the room that you're in.
Did you put the things on your wish list?
I hate to be doing that.
I put some lighting on it, but today I ordered.
a green screen like to put on the wall and that'll make the digital backgrounds like a lot
Be consistent with it though. And again, I'm sorry if I'm being overbearing or demanding, but I just like
I can see where you can go. I just do okay. I would love it to be more professional
But it's like still I got like just watching back these old episodes. I'm like, oh, like it's like I have a lot of like trolls
Like you've got you've got to make that room like just your state
Like where you like is that where you always sit when you do your stream? Yeah, it's me. It's me. It's definitely me
Hi, I like how are you?
I'm good what's good I know there's drama so I'm not gonna like some what do you think about um psyche is um title
I don't see what the title is.
Wait, hold on.
No, Alexa, stop.
Not you.
Alexandra.
Yeah.
Okay.
First, it was hot and beat.
It was hot and messy, beaters, whatever.
Hot and meaty.
He's been covering me all day long.
All fucking dope.
Like you asked me and I took your advice.
I took your advice, Alexandra.
You told us to take a break and keep, you know, in each other's lane.
It's nearly impossible. He's been restreaming my fucking content. I messaged him. I said don't cover my content
Okay, and then he started going and no I just want to give you a shout out because it does fucking hurt because a lot of people
That are my fucking friends
You don't see half of the shit that are being said about me
You know
What is your play your song again?
about like my fucking cousin and I'm crumbling biscuit and my teeth are falling apart.
Don't ever fucking sit here and play victim and fucking say anybody talked about your fucking
animals when I did nothing. I said nothing about your fucking animals. You really?
No, I will always keep it real.
I'm not that big of a fucking bully to use you as a title over and over because I want nothing to do with you.
It's okay, you can have my mutual friends, all respect to them.
No, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, oh.
Oh, but in a way, it's like, it just seems like...
gosh if you see some of the stuff that she's been doing i didn't know it was this serious see
it's just bad and then it's like we make up but and i love her and it's like i'm not mad i
but i think i hope she just some two conclusions because she thought i was i was like
Streaming her show today, which I was but it was like through a trip kick video. I'm just watching. I wasn't trying to like this or anything
Here's what I think she's upset about because I did I do I do know that there was a
Restream and I did see what it was about
Maybe be it if you if you're listening to this. I think I know what you really are upset about you cordially leave me the fuck alone
Psyche do not message me make some shit. Do not
if you need help or you think that like you need any kind of like you know just don't don't message me
ever again okay you're moderating me right now you are moderating me you came on my fucking
channel you introduced yourself on my fucking channel i brought everybody to you okay you
And don't let me fucking put it out there don't ever put me in that fucking don't ever put me in that predicament
Again, if you let people call me crazy and say I killed my mother and I fucked my cat and I fucked my uncle and all that shit, I'm gonna let people make their judgments about you.
But I always defended you. But you know what? I'll never message you like making you like fucking worried about me. I'll make sure of that.
Because I didn't mean, I was even insulting you.
No, you're always playing victim.
sort of you all of a sudden
Why are you putting your title under my name? It was beta and then you changed it. Why were you playing me all day long?
Why didn't you let go when people say we need a break? Why you did the same thing to fucking Emma?
You did the same to clumsy flamboyant. You did the same thing to Elisa
You're gonna suffocate the fuck out of fucking Alexander too
Well, you know, it's like people are free to talk to you. They want to like when they want. Yeah, you know what?
Don't make fucking listen Alexander has no knee for a while
Not once have I ever fucking mentioned her in a title not ever ever fucking use her content
How many times I've been madder of that I have to hold shit down and hold it in but you
You're such a victim boy that you need everybody's fucking help
everybody's fucking help
I'm a woman.
Peter, you can go ahead.
I have a side job.
I'm not here for money.
I'm here for fucking fun and content.
And you're saying I'm ruining your brand?
How about you're fucking breaking people's fucking heart?
What do I do?
When you're fucking monetary gain?
Are you mad because I because I'm doing the series? I'm not mad at you Alex at all
I I'm mad because this man used me and his name as
Title and he's like beat us me da beat us this beat up properly. He made a song. He's
Antigenizing me. Don't don't make any AI songs of beta because I don't even fucking mention me. I did that
No, it's okay, Alex. You did it. You did it one time months ago. He keeps doing it. He wants me to come here. He wants to do this. He is always playing fixum. He's manipulative. I swear to God, I'll read your messages and you're gonna fucking be outed.
No, don't do that.
Yeah, I'm the one coming here, but you're the one making titles about me and streaming about
Maybe I am a little bit hurt because you use and manipulate my fucking friends and they believe you're fucking bullshit
But I'm not gonna I'm gonna give them a heads up. I'm gonna give them a heads up
Beta beta have you in are you in psyche dating or are you friends?
We've never, we're not dating and like, I just didn't mean, she's not interested in me dating.
Wait, this is, because this is intense and I didn't, see, I, I feel like I, I, did I make this, I bet I made it worse.
Shit.
No, you're fine.
You this happens a million times they happen every other week
Because she's mad because I bet she feels like I took you away from her a little bit
I can tell be down. I'm sorry if you see this. I'm sorry, you know what
I'm sorry
When I really like them and I'm sorry beta that I I like kind of like
Pushed because I have the tendency to do that. I'm overly assertive
She she probably feels like I took you from her a little bit. That's what it is
Well, you guys talk all the time
We haven't talked very much, I haven't seen her, I was looking for a day, and she finally came on, and I finally kept going to her too.
I wasn't there.
I keep mentioning you?
Yeah, I kept doing the mod, it's like, it's not my obsession.
No, some of it's it's it's I think it's a few things going on. It just is I can tell
The psyche really cares about you a lot in case you hear this later
he really does he said nothing but good things about you to me he's never like psyche and i we don't
really talk a lot of camera um we've like dm'd you know like show plans which you know and then
i at the last minute changed it because i want to talk about ai and astrology so like i'm a little
I'm not very like talkative with people behind the scenes. So if you think that beta that's not the case
um, I think that I just kind of like
Probably made her upset because I got really excited about you because I just like you a lot
It probably pissed her off. I think that's what I think
Good for me to like lay off of her for like, you know, because I like having it like it's like she's not coming to the show
But we've been kind of fighting for like a few months now like like probably like
Like
Only have two other parts of the three-part series. Okay after Sunday
You didn't come to the last one. Thank you play this song show Alex you're beat is upset
Oh, no, I don't know. He doesn't want me to play that song
Set at me, but she doesn't want to say so
I don't know, if you don't feel like it, I think she's about to come talk, I mean, it's like,
I think it's possible.
I don't think we're out of anybody, it's like, just like, yeah, I don't think so, I don't think it is about it.
It's a little bit of that, maybe not like 90%, but like if you look at it like a pie chart, it's at least 20%.
Yeah, you know
Y'all talk about I don't know the rest you talk about it like streamer stuff like I think I think I'm a really good